<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

 <string name = 'wordpal' >Wordpal</string>
 <string name = 'settings' >Settings</string>
 <string name = 'de' >de</string>
 <string name = 'fa' >پا</string>
 <string name = 'i_know' >I know</string>
 <string name = 'not_sure' >Not sure</string>
 <string name = 'select_collection'>Select Collection</string>
 <string name = 'right_number'>Right Number : </string>
 <string name = 'empty_list_view_text_message'>Select at least one collection</string>
 <string name = 'score_'>Score : </string>
 <string name = 'refresh'>Refresh</string>
 <string name = 'exit'>Exit</string>
 <string name = 'shop_in_store'>Shop in store</string>
 <string name = 'view_archived'>View archived</string>
 <string name = 'reset_to_zero'>Reset to 0</string>
 <string name = 'buy'>Buy</string>
 <string name = 'view'>View</string>
 <string name = 'view_collection'>View collection</string>

 <string name = 'help'>Help</string>
 <string name = 'help_introduction'>
Welcome to Wordpal,\n
Wordpal is kind of <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Leitner_system">Leitner system</a>.\n
But a little bit different, since this is a Android program and we don\'t have a physical box here.\n
Instead we are using Collection concept, each Collection contains serveral words or sentences.\n
Let\'s show you this educational program thorugh snapshots.
Below snapshot is your first page, after opening this program.
 </string>
 <string name = 'help_snapshot_first_page'>
You could enter into this help page, either by selecting Menu->Help or bicycle icon on top right(if you could see it,
works in Android 3.0 and above).\n
First word you see is \'I\', which in Persian means من\n
You could see it\'s translation by selecting پا button\n
And in Deutsch means Ich, which is also could be visible by selecting de button.\n
To process further in this game, You either should select _I Know_ button or _Not Sure_ button.\n
If you could remember \'I\' menaining in both languages, then _I Know_ button should be selected,
otherwise select _Not Sure_.\n
In case you select _I Know_ button, then score for current word will increase by +1.
Usually you need to finish one round(which at the end you see Exit button).\n
It is recommended to take a break after each round.\n
Default score for moving words into archive(memorized) directory is 10, and you could change it to
 your desire number, depends to power of your short and long memory.\n
To change this right number, follwoing below snapshots:
 </string>
 <string name="help_snapshot_select_collection">
In addition each Collection could be selected or unselected, for start you have only one collection,
 named \'WordTrainer Lesson1: People - Personen\'. As you see in following snapshot this collection
 has green background, which means it is selected. You could unselect it by clicking on it, then
 background will change to white. To start a round, at least one collection should be selected.
 For adding more collection, you need to browse and buy a collection at shopping page(Menu->Shop in store). 
 </string>

</resources>